Thank you for watching!
Good morning
It's already night
I think you guys are doing your best in
live
We are doing our best
I'm going to order Uber
That's right
I have something to give you instead of
Uber
What is it?
I'm going to divide you into 3 people
and you guys are going to do a content
What is a content?
I have a script
but
I'm going to arrange the contents for
each team
That's a pain in the ass
I said it
The leader should say something like
that
I'm going to arrange it
and announce it at the end
You are going to announce it?
So, first, I'm going to divide you into
3 teams
and I'm going to give you the script
If you decide the team,
you can't be together
so, you are going to play rock-paper-
scissors
until you divide into 3 people
Rock-paper-scissors
Let's divide into 3 people
You are not going to say it
Oh, we divided
We divided
I think it's better to decide the team
name
What should I do?
Team name Kato Miria
OK?
Yes
Then, please decide the team name from
this side
Team name is
Dan-Sakuma-Uchikai
Cute
we are
cheering
tren
Us
, I
think I'm free today, but
thank you
I'll contact you suddenly
.
After this, everyone will practice with
the arrangement and contact you
suddenly, so
if you contact me, I will hold a
presentation.
Then, start practicing
together.
Do you remember that I gave you a
script a while ago?
What did you give me?
What is this?
I told you to practice and arrange the
script, and I called you out suddenly.
So I called you out.
I didn't know it was today.
So this time, the person who made the
script will be judged.
The group of three was divided into
three, and the group of three was chosen
by the judges.
The winner is Queen of Conte.
What is that?
I don't know what it is.
What is the prize?
There is no prize.
I can't do it without a prize.
I can't do it.
I'm still a kid.
I don't want to be an idol who is at
the same level as me.
The three teams will play rock-paper-
scissors.
The third group to be announced at the
end of the game will be the first to do
the script.
Our team will do our best.
I can do it.
What is the team name?
Fua Fua Pippi
Fuwa Fuwa Pippi
I can only get one word.
The third group to be announced at the
end of the game will be the first to do
the script.
I'll give you some snacks later.
What is the team name?
The first team to be announced at the
end of the game will be the first to do
the script.
The third group to be announced at the
end of the game will be the first to do
the script.
I can do it.
You can still choose the second or
third team.
I want to do it.
Which team do you choose?
I choose the second team.
We will announce the team name in the
group.
The first team to be announced at the
end of the game will be the first to do
the script.
What's the name?
The first team to be announced at the
end of the game will be the first to do
the script.
Let's get started.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Bank robbery.
We are going to rob a bank today.
We can't fail.
Are you ready?
Yes, of course.
Boss, leave it to me.
First, we check the luggage.
Show me your weapon.
What kind of weapon will come out?
No, no, no.
We can't rob a bank with this.
This is a toy.
I bought this at 100 yen.
100 yen?
It's not 108 yen.
No, it's not.
I bought a plastic bag, so it's 113
yen.
It doesn't change.
Please collect it later.
Bank robbery.
It doesn't work.
What is this?
Bang, bang.
You are completely licking.
I said, but I want to collect 10 yen
coins.
10 yen coins?
Bang, bang.
Boss!
Let's break in.
You idiot!
This is not a game. This is a robbery.
Get a grip.
I'm sorry.
You guys don't need any weapons. Leave
the weapons to me.
And you can't show your faces, right?
So, prepare some masks.
You brought them, right?
Yes, we did.
Bang, bang. Bang, bang.
I need to get my clothes matched.
I wonder what kind of clothes I'll get.
Are you ready?
Thank you for your viewing.
Is it okay?
Yes!
Good answer!
Okay, let's go!
Yes!
No, let me see it!
Thank you very much!
Contra! Bank robbery!
Good morning.
You guys!
Today, we are going to rob Ihinari
Bank.
We will not let you fail.
Are you ready?
Of course, boss!
Leave it to me, boss!
Boss?
OK, it seems you are ready.
I will check your belongings, so show
me the weapons you brought.
Yes, boss!
This is it!
Magic wand!
You don't have a wand, do you?
That's why I need it.
I see.
Good.
Let's practice with it.
Yes!
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Are you really going to use magic?
I want to catch you!
Judo, I'll catch you!
Good!
OK!
Nice!
Do you want to try another weapon?
Yes!
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Next time, I'll use magic.
I want to use it as it is!
That's the best!
You're so innocent!
You're the boss, aren't you?
You're in the opposite position.
What did you bring?
I brought this.
It's a pistol.
I've never seen a pistol in a boy.
It's a standard.
I wonder if it's okay.
Am I weird?
It's okay.
I'll start from here.
You can't make a sound.
I'll go quietly.
Let's go!
Don't swim!
You'll find out what I'm thinking.
What are you doing?
I'm weird.
You guys!
Give me a call!
Put your hands up!
This is a live venue!
What are you doing?
I can't leave it to you.
Leave it to me.
I'll start from here.
Follow me.
Let's go!
Stop it!
Thank you for watching!
Yay!
Today is bank robbery!
Why are you laughing?
Say something to apologize.
I'm sorry.
You laughed.
He will be angry if we don't give it
back.
We'll start 3 seconds before.
Turn around!
Left!
Right!
Turn around!
Ready!
3 seconds!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Go!
Let's go eat!
The end
خر Вас
We'll be waiting!
We're going to the bank today.
Are you ready?
It's far.
I'm nervous.
It's your first time.
Calm down. Leave it to me.
Thank you.
Let's check what we have.
Let's see your weapons.
Leave it to me.
What kind of weapons will come out?
I bought a brush.
It's cute.
Please keep it.
Why?
It's cute.
You'll like it.
What are you doing?
It's a brush.
Isn't today the day of the robbery with
the bank?
No, it's not.
Today is the day of the robbery.
It's true that I'm going to the bank,
but it's not.
The robbery with the bank?
That's not the case.
It's not the robbery with the bank, but
it's the bank.
The bank robbery.
That's enough.
I want to go to the bank robbery with a
makeup tool.
I want to wear it, but I'm wearing it
today.
Wait a minute.
The eye shadow is a little blurred.
Can I ask you to do it?
It's good.
Thank you.
I'm going to rap.
It's fine.
I don't want to go to the school
reunion.
I want to go to the school reunion.
Don't step on me.
It's fine.
Today is a robbery.
I was checking the weapons.
Can you prepare the weapons?
Yes.
What kind of weapons do you make?
I may have forgotten the gun.
What are you doing?
I was planning to go to the school
reunion.
What should I do?
I will call my father.
Please wait a minute.
It's a family of robberies.
I'm looking forward to what kind of
weapons will come out.
Dad, I forgot the gun today.
Can you lend it to me?
Your father is a police officer.
What?
Wait a minute.
If your father is a police officer, we
will be arrested.
But my father is a police officer.
We are going to a robbery.
If my father is a police officer, we
will be arrested.
What kind of family is it if my father
is a police officer and my daughter is a
robber?
It's a little complicated.
It may be complicated.
It's okay.
I don't need weapons.
Can you lend it to me?
But...
The bank I'm going to today is my
mother's bank.
I think my mother will give me money.
Really?
If you do that, will you steal your
mother's money?
I think it's the most complicated.
You are a bad person.
I recommend it.
I will be careful.
I can't be careful.
Leave the weapons to me.
Thank you.
I'm quick-witted.
I'll prepare the weapons.
You prepare the clothes for the
robbery.
Yes.
What will come out?
I don't have a weapon.
I'm a police officer.
I can't think of anything.
I think I'm in.
I'm sorry.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Show me!
Ready, set, go!
It's the same!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Today, we have a scriptwriter here.
We had a screening.
Please tell us the order of your
presentation.
Let's start with the first one.
Thank you for your hard work, Nixie and
Ijin.
It was very interesting.
I enjoyed watching Nixie's world view.
I also enjoyed Kachibana's noisy
movements.
The story is about a bird. It's a story
about a bird.
It was a good story.
Thank you very much.
It was great.
Let's move on to the second one.
The second one is called Bird's
Cartilage with Village.
It's a story about a village.
It was very interesting.
I think I made a bad Fuji-Tan.
I was worried about the long story.
I was wondering what I was shown in the
second half.
I was winning the semi-final, but I was
wondering why I changed the story in the
final.
I'm looking forward to the next time.
Well then, last time, trigger three,
please.
Yup!
See you next time on Danshoku Man!
It was very interesting.
The first time I saw the hair-raising
scene,
I thought it was a scene where teenage
girls were using themselves.
I thought it was very easy to get into.
The story developed from the middle,
and the story developed unexpectedly.
I think it was very good that I got
into the world of the content.
That's all.
We've had three judges vote.
This time, we're going to decide the
queen of contos.
I'd like to ask the judges which one
was the best.
The group chosen for the queen of
contos is...
This one!
Magic Stick!
Here we go!
I only have my uncle's bread.
Banker's... robber's silver...
Ta-da!
It's a match!
Yeah!
I did it!
I didn't expect that!
I matched it this morning!
That was quick!
I'm glad I won.
Thank you for watching.
Ughhhh!!!!
I'm scared.
I can smell it.
Amazing.
The next episode is called Queen
Contest.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
So, the second time...
Is it possible?
It was a sudden Queen Yogo Contest
final.
Congratulations!
The winner of the second time is...
Kana!
Congratulations!
See you next week!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!